https://www.petsafe.net/privacy

Opting Out
California Privacy Rights (“Shine the Light” Law) and California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA)
Privacy Shield Dissolution
Personal Data of EU and Swiss Residents
Controllers and Processors
North America
International operations (specifically EU)
Product and Marketing Research
3rd Party Processing containing Personal Data of EU and Swiss Residents
Google Analytics
Google Tag Manager (GTM)
Google Ads (AdWords)
Rackspace
Microsoft Azure (Hosting)
Amazon AWS (Hosting)
Do Not Track Requests
RADIO SYSTEMS CORPORATION:
PRIVACY, COOKIE, and DATA PROCESSING POLICY
This document was last updated September 1, 2020.
General
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you how Radio Systems Corporation, its brands including, but not limited to PetSafe®, SportDOG®, Invisible Fence®, Premier Pet®, Free Spirit® brand, Kurgo and its affiliates (collectively referred to as "RSC", “we”, “us”, “our(s)”), gathers, uses and shares information about you. We appreciate your trust that we will do so cautiously.
This Privacy Policy includes but is not limited to RSC “Website”, “Websites”, “WebPage”, “WebPages”, “Web Page”, “Web Pages”, “Page”, “Pages”, “Site”, “Sites”, “Service” “Services”, “Mobile Apps”, “Mobile Applications”, “Smart Products”.
You may contact us at Attn: Risk Management, Radio Systems Corporation, 10427 PetSafe Way, Knoxville, TN 37932 or you may send an e-mail to privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com.
Inquires made by email may be responded to by email, the sender is consenting to return replies by email unless it is specified to return communications through another method.
This Privacy and Cookie Policy may be changed over time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon the posting of the modified Privacy and Cookie Policy. Users of the Website are advised to regularly read the Privacy and Cookie Policy for possible changes
Data Usage
RSC’s primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience and to assist with purchasing, ordering, and support. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to improve your experience.
RSC only processes personal data that a user voluntarily consents to provide to RSC. This information may include your name, date of birth, gender, address, IP addresses, product details, equipment or device, GPS coordinates or location data, additional usage and device data may be collected through the use of "Smart Products” and "Mobile Apps".
We may require you to create an “Account” or "Smart Product Account" prior to using services, purchasing items through the website, registering your product, registering or accessing warranty information, registering for any contest, or other content submission.
We ask that you provide us with certain information during the registration process. While you are not required to do so, if you are unable or unwilling to do so, you will not be able to complete the registration process, and therefore you will not be able to access and use certain information, material and services.
Additionally, we will use personal data and communication preferences to determine the best method to communicate with you in regard to your account or services.
Personal data may be used in investigations related to violations of policy, terms and service agreements, acceptable usage, and unauthorized or attempted unauthorized access. Legal and regulatory reporting including where disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action regarding injury or interference with the rights and property of RSC.
Inquiries and Complaints
You may contact us at Attn: Risk Management, Radio Systems Corporation, 10427 PetSafe Way, Knoxville, TN 37932 or you may send an e-mail to privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com.
Inquires made by email may be responded to by email, the sender is consenting to return replies by email unless it is specified to return communications through another method.
Children's Privacy
We take children's privacy seriously. This Website is not directed to children. We do not seek to collect personal information about children through our Website. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If we learn that someone under the age of 18 has submitted information to us through any part of our Website, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that can be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and removed the information, we will honor that request.
Acquisitions and Other Reorganizations
Information collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy, including Protected Personal Information, may be disclosed to one or more third parties in connection with any change of ownership or control in RSC’s business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), or any other reorganization or joint venture, or assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceeding), and any such information may be used by such third party in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Equally, information collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy, including Personal Information, may be disclosed to one or more third parties in connection with any acquisition or merger carried out by RSC of such third parties.
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the terms in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. In the unlikely event that RSC or substantially all its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.
Security
Perfect security does not exist on the internet and we cannot guarantee anyone complete security. Your privacy is important to us and we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private and would never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You understand that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collected from this Website. Please note that emails, messages sent via your web browser, and other similar means of communication with other users, are not encrypted. We strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential or sensitive information through these means. Please also be aware that we may use third-party cloud service providers that provide hosting, data storage and other services pursuant to standard terms and conditions that may be nonnegotiable; these service providers have informed us or the public that they apply security measures they consider adequate for the protection of information within their system, or they have a general reputation for applying such measures. However, we will not be liable (to the fullest extent permitted by law) for any damages that may result from the misuse of any information, including Personal Information, by these companies.
Links to Third-Party Sites / Products / Services
This Website may contain links to other sites. When you click on such links, you may leave our Site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on this Website. “Smart Devices” may contain features to integrate or share data with 3rd parties, if sharing data with a 3rd party please refer to that company’s privacy policy.
WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, DISCLOSURE OR OTHER PRIVACY PRACTICES OF ANY THIRD PARTY, INCLUDING OUR AFFILIATES, THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, ANY EMPLOYERS (INCLUDING ANY EMPLOYER THAT PROVIDES A COMPANY PAGE), ANY THIRD-PARTY SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORM, ANY THIRD PARTY MAKING AVAILABLE THE DEVICES OR OPERATING SYSTEMS FOR WHICH THE SITE IS AVAILABLE, AND ANY THIRD PARTY OPERATING ANY WEBSITE TO WHICH THE SITE CONTAINS A LINK. YOU MAY HAVE RIGHTS DIRECTLY ENFORCEABLE AGAINST THESE THIRD PARTIES, SO YOU SHOULD CONSIDER THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES TO LEARN MORE.
Legal Requests
Radio Systems cooperates with law enforcement and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights.
In response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or other alleged improper or illegal activity, we may disclose information relevant to the investigation including, but not limited to, name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, IP address, user history and complaints.
Legal and regulatory reporting where disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action regarding injury or safety interference with the rights and property of RSC.
Without limiting the above, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other third parties, except as specifically outlined in this Privacy Policy, without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of this information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merge with another company.
This includes but is not limited to the following:
RSC is committed to cooperating with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDIC) and comply with the advice given by such authorities regarding human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of the employment relationship.
RSC is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC)
You may contact us at Attn: Risk Management, Radio Systems Corporation, 10427 PetSafe Way, Knoxville, TN 37932 or you may send an e-mail to privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com
Access, Correction and Removal of Personal Data
You can request RSC to provide access to the personal data it has collected about you at any time.
You can also request RSC to provide a report of, correct, or to delete such personal data. Please send an email to privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com or visit https://www.radiosystemscorporation.com/personal-data-request in case you have any questions concerning your personal data.
This Privacy and Cookie Policy may be changed over time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon the posting of the modified Privacy and Cookie Policy. Users of the Website are advised to regularly read the Privacy and Cookie Policy for possible changes.
For international (Specifically EU) please contact Luzern:
Luzern Technology Solutions Ltd. Blanchardstown Business & Technology Park, Snugborough Road, Blanchardstown, Dublin 15, Ireland. Co. Reg. #361832, Dublin, Ireland.
Website: http://www.luzern.co/privacy-policy/
Email: info@luzern.co
Opting Out
Individuals may have the right to limit the use and disclosure of their personal information as required by the Privacy Shield’s Principles, such as whether your personal information is disclosed to a third party or used for purposes materially different from the purpose for which the personal information was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. If you wish to limit the use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles, please contact us at privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com.
Please note that we may still send other messages to you, such as administrative messages. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.
California Privacy Rights (“Shine the Light” Law) and California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA)
RSC does not sell personal data. RSC does not purchase / procure any personal data from re-sellers.
California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing use. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2016 will receive information regarding 2015 sharing activities).
No special pricing or incentives will be provided based on “opt-in” or “consent” status. Right to notice, Right to Access, Right to Know, Right to Opt-Out, and Right to Delete will be handled the same as GDPR Data Subject Requests, please see the “Access, Correction and Removal of Personal Data” section of this policy for more detail.
Privacy Shield Dissolution
At RSC we are aware of and continue to monitor changes associated with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield (Privacy Shield). While we are actively certified and in good standing with Privacy Shield, we do not solely rely on Privacy Shield for data transfers between the European Union and the United States.
We currently have and will continue to ensure that Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs) and/or Binding Corporate Rules (BCRs) are in place to ensure continuity of cross-border data transfers. In addition, RSC utilizes a Data Protection Agreement (DPA) with vendors and 3rd parties to ensure Data Security Standards (DSS) are in place.
“On July 16, 2020, the Court of Justice of the European Union issued a judgment declaring as “invalid” the European Commission’s Decision (EU) 2016/1250 of 12 July 2016 on the adequacy of the protection provided by the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield. As a result of that decision, the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework is no longer a valid mechanism to comply with EU data protection requirements when transferring personal data from the European Union to the United States. This decision does not relieve participants in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield of their obligations under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.”
https://www.privacyshield.gov/Program-Overview
Personal Data of EU and Swiss Residents
The following section pertains to users which are in the European Union and Switzerland. RSC will transfer certain data to RSC in the United States. RSC will comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States.
RSC has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, and Purpose Limitation, Access, Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.
In the context of an onward transfer of data to a third party, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. RSC shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless RSC proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
Residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland have a right of access to their data. If you wish RSC to access and edit such data on your behalf, identity verification may be required to authorize transactions.
European Economic Area and Switzerland residents also have a right, if their personal data is inaccurate, of rectification, erasure or blocking of such inaccurate personal data. You may alternatively request RSC to rectify, erase or block the data by sending a certified letter, with a copy of your passport or national identity card (for identity verification purposes), to the above address with the exact nature of the requested action.
Controllers and Processors
RSC operates under the following lawful basis: Consent, Contract, Legal Obligation, and Processing not requiring identification. More specific information about these lawful bases can be found at https://gdpr-info.eu/art-6-gdpr/
North America
Risk Management, Radio Systems Corporation, 10427 PetSafe Way, Knoxville, TN 37932 (“RSC”) is the controller of all personal data collected.
International operations (specifically EU)
Luzern Technology Solutions Ltd (“Luzern”) is the controller of all personal data collected:
Luzern Technology Solutions Ltd. Blanchardstown Business & Technology Park, Snugborough Road, Blanchardstown, Dublin 15, Ireland. Co. Reg. #361832, Dublin, Ireland.
Website: http://www.luzern.co/privacy-policy/
Email: info@luzern.co
Product and Marketing Research
May be performed by The Research House, A Schlesinger Company. Where The Research House is utilized, RSC is a processor of the data.
WebSite: https://www.schlesingergroup.com/en/legal/privacy/#privacy-policy
Contact Information:
Help@InspiredOpinions.com
+1 (855) 244-0886
InspiredOpinions, Privacy Inquiries
101 Wood Avenue South, Suite 501, Iselin, NJ 08830
3rd Party Processing containing Personal Data of EU and Swiss Residents
RSC may utilize 3rd parties to assist with certain functions of the business. This may include hosting of RSC systems and / or processing activities which may include personal data processing. 3rd parties are inspected for and are expected to comply with all applicable laws governing Protected Personal Data including but not limited to General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), applicable Data Protection Acts, and Privacy Shield regulations including but not limited to the transport of data.
For international (Specifically EU) please contact Luzern:
Luzern Technology Solutions Ltd. Blanchardstown Business & Technology Park, Snugborough Road, Blanchardstown, Dublin 15, Ireland. Co. Reg. #361832, Dublin, Ireland.
Website: http://www.luzern.co/privacy-policy/
Email: info@luzern.co
Independent Dispute Resolution
In compliance with the US-EU and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, RSC commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact RSC at:
Attn: Risk Management, Radio Systems Corporation, 10427 PetSafe Way, Knoxville, TN 37932, or by emailing privacy-dept@radiosystemcorporation.com.
There may be a possibility, under certain limited conditions, for EU and Swiss individuals to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel.
RSC has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles to the JAMS. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for more information and to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.
There may be a possibility, under certain limited conditions, for EU and Swiss individuals to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel.
Cookies Policy
This policy helps to explain the occasions when and why cookies may be sent to visitors to the Website (referred to in this policy as “we”, “us” or “our”). “Cookies” are text-only pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive or other website-browsing equipment for record-keeping purposes.
While using our Website we may store and access these cookies on your device. Accepting these cookies may be required for proper functionality of the website. While you have the right to prevent cookies from being created and stored we cannot guarantee how our site will perform for you.
Cookies allow the Website to remember essential information that will make your use of the site more convenient. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a randomly generated unique number or other value. Certain cookies will be used on the Site regardless of whether you are logged in to your account or not.
Like most websites, we use cookies for a variety of purposes, primarily to improve your online experience, for analytics and for marketing, and marketplace functionality.
We may specifically we use Cookies on the Website for the following purposes:
Analytical Purposes
We use cookies to analyze user activity to enable us to improve the website usage experience. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze include:
Your Device’s unique device ID
IP and/or MAC addresses
Pixel Tags
The domain from which you access the internet
The kind of browser or Device you use
Your Device’s operating system
The address of the internet site, banner or email from which you selected or entered a link that brought you to this Website
The number of links you click within this Website
The state or country from which you accessed this Website
The date and time of your visit and how long you spent visiting the Website
The pages you viewed on the Website
Purchase history
Interactions within the Website or App you are using
Preferences
We may use Cookies to store certain user preferences on our Website. For example, we may store the recent searches you have performed in a Cookie so that we can allow you to easily repeat those searches when you return to our Website.
Session Cookies
Temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the Website.
Persistent Cookies
Remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). When we use session cookies to track the total number of visitors to our Website, this is done on an anonymous aggregate basis (as cookies do not in themselves carry any personal data). We may also employ cookies so that we remember your computer when it is used to return to the Website to help customize your RSC web experience.
Communication Cookies
Allow cookies of third-party social networks (e.g. Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, LinkedIn). This enables a user to share content of the Website on social networks. These third parties may use cookies, but their use of cookies will not be governed by this Cookie Policy.
Performance cookies
Help us to understand the behavior of our visitors and the usage of the Website. This allows us to continuously improve the Website to provide you the best website experience.
Some cookies are managed by third parties, and you may refer to the third parties' own website privacy notifications for further information.
We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances. Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. You can easily delete any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser.
Furthermore, you can prevent Google's collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB# .This link creates an opt-out cookie which prevents the further processing of your data.
To block Google Analytics cookies specifically, you can install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provided by Google.
3rd Party Web Service Providers
Netlify
Our hosting provider Netlify collects website access data that includes IP addresses for the purposes of preventing attacks and abuse. That data is inaccessible to RSC and, as per Netlify’s GDPR compliance information, is deleted within 30 days. Netlify, when you submit a form on our page, Netlify collects your IP address for the purpose of preventing spam and abuse. RSC has access to submitted form data, including IP addresses, that you submit. We do not use your IP address collected in this way for any purpose, including processing, helping to support your request, or marketing. All data submitted to RSC is handled in accordance with RSC Privacy Policy.
For questions regarding Netlify’s data processing handling, please visit the Netlify directly via the https://www.netlify.com/support/.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics cookies to obtain an overall view of visitor habits and visitor volumes, and to help improve the overall experience on our website.
Google Analytics uses "performance cookies" and "targeting cookies" to analyze how you use the Website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers.
We utilize Google Analytics with the expansion '_anonymizeIp()' which means that Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address.
You can find more information on the _anonymizeIp() expansion from Google Analytics Help Page, specifically https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en
On behalf of us, Google will use the information collected for the purpose of evaluating your use of our Website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to us. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
You can prevent Google's collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB# .This link creates an opt-out cookie which prevents the further processing of your data.
To block Google Analytics cookies specifically, you can install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provided by Google.
Google Tag Manager (GTM)
Google Tag Manager is a tag management system (TMS) that allows you to quickly and easily update measurement codes and related code fragments collectively known as tags on your website or mobile app. Once the small segment of Tag Manager code has been added to your project, you can safely and easily deploy analytics and measurement tag configurations from a web-based user interface.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Google Ads (AdWords)
Google Ads (formerly Google AdWords and Google AdWords Express) is an online advertising solution that businesses use to promote their products and services on Google Search, YouTube, and other sites across the web. Google Ads also allows advertisers to choose specific goals for their ads, like driving phone calls or website visits. With a Google Ads account, advertisers can customize their budgets and targeting, and start or stop their ads at any time.
You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads
Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Bing Ads Remarketing
Bing Ads remarketing service is provided by Microsoft Inc.
You can opt-out of Bing Ads interest-based ads by following their instructions: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Microsoft by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/PrivacyStatement
Twitter
Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.
You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405
You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://twitter.com/privacy
Facebook
Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.
You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950
To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads, follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217
Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through opt-out using your mobile device settings or:
Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/
Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/
For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
Pinterest
Pinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc.
You can opt-out from Pinterest's interest-based ads by enabling the "Do Not Track" functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions: http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data
You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy
Paylocity
Online job applications are processed through Paylocity.
https://www.paylocity.com/privacy-policy/
You may additionally contact Paylocity directly at privacy@paylocity.com
Hubspot
Marketing, sales, and service software.
https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy
Rackspace
May be used as an email hosting provider.
https://www.rackspace.com/en-us/gdpr
Microsoft Azure (Hosting)
May be used to host RSC Servers, Sites and/or Functions.
https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement
Amazon AWS (Hosting)
May be used to host RSC Servers, Sites and/or Functions.
https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/gdpr-center/
3rd Party Payment Providers
RSC uses several payment processors. Information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.
RSC may retain some card data to make shopping easier for users, and as required for validation and regulatory requirements. RSC does not store Sensitive Authentication Data as defined by PCI. This includes (magnetic strip, or equivalent on a chip), PINs, PIN Blocks, CAV, PAN CVC, CVV, CSV, CID, CAV2, PAN CVC2, CVV2.
You may see PCI’s definition of Sensitive Authentication Data, https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/pci_security/glossary#S
PayPal / Braintree
https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Stripe
https://stripe.com/privacy
Chase Paymentech
https://merchantservices.chase.com/online-privacy-policy
Oracle Vantiv
https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/
App Frontier Chargent
https://www.appfrontier.com/privacy.html
Blackthorn.io
https://app.termly.io/document/privacy-policy/39abcd83-854c-40fa-8c62-3686c08e56f2
3rd Party Shipping Providers
Mailing Address, and contact information including (if provided) name, email, and phone number will be provided to the 3rd party to fulfill shipping requirements.
These providers include but may not be limited to Geodis, Amazon, UPS, FEDEX, US Postal Service.
Do Not Track Requests
We do not respond to the browser “Do Not Track” (DNT) signal if enabled by the user in their web browser. When we set or read cookies on non-RSC sites that have integrated our features, we do so. We do not share any information about your use of RSC with those third parties. When third parties that we have integrated into RSC sites (as described in the RSC Cookie Policy) set or read their own third-party cookies, they may or may not respond to the DNT signal.
Customer Care
1-866-738-4379
Live Chat
Chat Offline
Send an Email
Manuals & Support
Authorized Online Retailers
Find a Retailer
©2020 Radio Systems Corporation All Rights Reserved.
Privacy |
Wholesalers |
Affiliates
You're browsing our US site. Would you like to visit our International site?
Yes
No
